<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Some questions from a newbie</title>
		<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13500508/some-questions-from-a-newbie</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Some questions from a newbie&quot; - after looking through the wiki i have some beginner questions.</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 01:01:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13500508#post-4730456</guid>
				<title>Re: Some questions from a newbie</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13500508/some-questions-from-a-newbie#post-4730456</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 22:48:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>The UA feats have been added, I think the reason for the feats taking a while to appear is due to how adding things to the front page requires admin privs, so even if the page exists it takes some time</p> <p>The blood hunter is also now on the main page.</p> <p>So yeah. Often the pages do exist, but are currently 'Orphaned' and unaccessible from the main page, for example the new UA feats from this month.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13500508#post-4712618</guid>
				<title>Some questions from a newbie</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13500508/some-questions-from-a-newbie#post-4712618</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 21:38:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Puffington</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6185284</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I've have been an avid dnd nerd and love this site, there are some conundrums that i've found out though. Maybe there are some specifik rules of why things are like they are? i don't know. please enlighten me on these things.</p> <ul> <li><strong>Blood hunter</strong>: is there a specific reason why blood hunter is not on the main page? even though the class came after some time i think it would be great if new people saw all the available classes from the start and not only the main classes. it becomes easily forgotten otherwise. should there be an icon for the blood hunter?</li> </ul> <ul> <li><strong>telepathy feat (UA)</strong> i found this feat existing on the page though with no connection to the &quot;feat&quot; list on the home page. Are (UA) feats not used or has it just been neglected?</li> <li><strong>telekenetic feat (UA)</strong> same thing as the telepathy feat</li> <li><strong>tower of iron will feat (UA)</strong></li> <li><strong>Wild talent feat (UA)</strong></li> </ul> <ul> <li><strong>psionic soul sorcerer subclass</strong> found out that this thing existed. Should maybe put in sorcerer subclass column.</li> </ul> <p>Thank you for your time :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>