<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Unlinked Articles and Page Consolidation</title>
		<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13873074/unlinked-articles-and-page-consolidation</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Unlinked Articles and Page Consolidation&quot; - What to do with unlinked articles? And should we have pages for each source?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:59:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13873074#post-4957431</guid>
				<title>Re: Unlinked Articles and Page Consolidation</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13873074/unlinked-articles-and-page-consolidation#post-4957431</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 12:25:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fredbob711</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6144441</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I think a description of the book and a link to the D&amp;D Beyond page for now would work.</p> <p>I'm a little leery of putting too much story-type content on the page because I don't know what might bring the page to WotC's attention and prompt any kind of takedown notice. I don't even know if they care considering the amount of content that's already up here&#8230; what does everyone else think?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13873074#post-4956252</guid>
				<title>Re: Unlinked Articles and Page Consolidation</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13873074/unlinked-articles-and-page-consolidation#post-4956252</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2021 02:00:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Out of Time</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>4858050</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I've got quite a bit of time on my hands, is it ok to start making pages for each source?<br /> Starting out, I'd probably just put a short description of the sourcebook, maybe a link to its DnD Beyond page, its date of release, and as many of the articles that have come from it as I can find through the search feature, and perhaps even the original text of the plane shift articles, or maybe just link their pages.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13873074#post-4827007</guid>
				<title>Re: Unlinked Articles and Page Consolidation</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13873074/unlinked-articles-and-page-consolidation#post-4827007</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 13:35:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fredbob711</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6144441</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I didn't know those pages existed.</p> <p>We can look into individual sourcebook pages as well as a site map/directory.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13873074#post-4826832</guid>
				<title>Unlinked Articles and Page Consolidation</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-13873074/unlinked-articles-and-page-consolidation#post-4826832</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 09:57:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Out of Time</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>4858050</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>It has come to my attention that this wiki has some unlinked pages, some of which have a lot of text, like the pages for the plane shift planes, which are sources for some major things like subclasses, sometimes spells, and feats. They are currently only accessible through specific searches of the wiki's search bar. It would be convenient for there to be a page organizing each link in the wiki into groups, like the main page, but more expansive.</p> <p>Also, directory with pages for each of the major sourcebooks and the things stemming from them would be useful to people who can use only a few sources, like people participating in adventurer's league. Also, links from each page in a sourcebook linking back to their sourcebook page would tie everything neatly together.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>