<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Homebrew Subclasses</title>
		<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14039632/homebrew-subclasses</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Homebrew Subclasses&quot; - Should we keep the homebrew subclasses from Mike Mearls&#039; ThinkDM/Twitter?</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 01:00:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14039632#post-4951448</guid>
				<title>Re: Homebrew Subclasses</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14039632/homebrew-subclasses#post-4951448</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 15:46:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Dont really have strong reasons or arguments to keep them personally, and yeah the mike mearls stuff is a bit unbalanced. If you want it to go its fair for it do so. Id probably only miss them on the account of them having been here for a while and me getting used to their presence, but yeah, its fair game for them to be removed most probably</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14039632#post-4942776</guid>
				<title>Re: Homebrew Subclasses</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14039632/homebrew-subclasses#post-4942776</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 08:14:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Out of Time</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>4858050</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Yeah, I feel like the Mike Mearls stuff should be taken off. Its already accessible on twitter, and all the others all have strong reasons</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14039632#post-4942501</guid>
				<title>Homebrew Subclasses</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14039632/homebrew-subclasses#post-4942501</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 02 Apr 2021 01:40:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>cottoneyenoh</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>5928724</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So I've been thinking a lot about homebrew recently, and it led me to consider what homebrew we host on this site. We currently have 4 types of homebrew: Critical Role/Matthew Mercer's creations, D&amp;DBeyond partnered content, content from Exploring Eberron (created by Eberron setting creator Keith Baker), and 3 subclasses created by Mike Mearls, shared either on his Twitter or his blog, ThinkDM.</p> <p>I strongly believe that the D&amp;DBeyond partnered content like the Wild Card and Renegade belong here as they are no longer easily accessible in other places and were intended to be made more available before things broke bad between Riot Games and WOTC. I also support keeping Critical Role content on here as it is one of the most popular pieces of D&amp;D content in existence. I'm even willing to keep Keith Baker's work since it was revised and published on DMsGuild and maintains the position as #1 most popular title.</p> <p>However, Mike Mearls' <a href="http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/cleric:beauty">Cleric: Beauty Domain</a>, <a href="http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/monk:soul-knife">Monk: Way of the Soul Knife</a>, and <a href="http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/warlock:kraken">Warlock: Kraken Patron</a> all seem to be out of place. For starters, I initially assumed that the Monk and Warlock subclasses were some form of typo given the UA and eventual publishing of the Rogue's Soul Knife archetype and the Warlock's Fathomless patron. The Way of the Soul Knife and the Kraken, published by Mike Mearls, seemed to be conceptual, building up to the release of those subclasses as UA. Additionally, in Mearls' own words, &quot;The Beauty domain is a little bonkers, probably too nutty for a print product.&quot; He published it on his twitter as a concept along with two other domains: Destruction and Darkness (neither of which we have available on our page).</p> <p>I suppose I'm just curious if anyone has strong feelings one way or another regarding Mearls' &quot;homebrew&quot; staying in the wiki. I've never seen anyone discuss them, and most of the edits on two of them were from me (the Beauty domain isn't even on the main page, and no one's brought it up clamoring for it's inclusion). Just a question that's been nagging at me while I wait for a pdf of Candlekeep Mysteries to become available so I can add anything to the items page ¯\_ (ツ)_/¯</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>