<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Should Blood Hunter be moved to the Homebrew section?</title>
		<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14022594/should-blood-hunter-be-moved-to-the-homebrew-section</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Should Blood Hunter be moved to the Homebrew section?&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:58:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14022594#post-4922316</guid>
				<title>Re: Should Blood Hunter be moved to the Homebrew section?</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14022594/should-blood-hunter-be-moved-to-the-homebrew-section#post-4922316</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 12:06:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So then I assume the best path moving forwards would be to leave bloodhunter where it is then? I agree to that</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14022594#post-4922002</guid>
				<title>Re: Should Blood Hunter be moved to the Homebrew section?</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14022594/should-blood-hunter-be-moved-to-the-homebrew-section#post-4922002</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 01:19:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fredbob711</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6144441</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Blood Hunter is a tricky one because it is a well-developed and (from what I can tell) somewhat popular class option. I lean towards leaving it where it is since it does specify it is homebrew and it is the only full-on homebrew class that's on the site period. But it also doesn't really match up with what we've done with everything else on the main page. Homebrew is a weird category and is kind of just up to the discretion of editors and admins.</p> <p>Mystic and Rune Scribe were moved because it was actually flat-out stated by WotC that they would not be moving forward with either concept. They abandoned the idea of prestige classes for 5e (bye bye Rune Scribe) and stated that the Mystic class was too powerful and eventually folded some of the concepts into the subclasses in Tasha's.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14022594#post-4921004</guid>
				<title>Re: Should Blood Hunter be moved to the Homebrew section?</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14022594/should-blood-hunter-be-moved-to-the-homebrew-section#post-4921004</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 23:46:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I personally think not, since, despite the Bloodhunter technically being a homebrew class, it has had enough support from the community and attention for it to be treated as a true base game class, even if it is technically not. So even if its a little strange, I personally feel it makes sense to be listed amongst the base game classes</p> <p>As for the mystic and runescribe? well, the reason i think for it being moved was mostly out of lack of interest from the community. despite being official, the rune scribe was mostly forgotten and the mystic was actively ignored, which is why it made sense to move them to the obsolete UA section</p> <p>And besides, the bloodhunter does actively announce that it is homebrew right on the frontpage,</p> <p>so yeah</p> <p>while from a logical perspective its sorta weird, it makes sense for it to be listed on the frontpage</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14022594#post-4920752</guid>
				<title>Re: Should Blood Hunter be moved to the Homebrew section?</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14022594/should-blood-hunter-be-moved-to-the-homebrew-section#post-4920752</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 17:19:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>cottoneyenoh</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>5928724</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I think if Blood Hunter is moved to the Homebrew section, it would need to be retitled something like &quot;Homebrew Classes/Subclasses&quot; and just placed with the rest of them, much like how the Mystic and Rune Scribe are placed in the archived UA section. I think that moving it to the Homebrew section would be consistent with how we're formatting the front page, but I also understand that its popularity could lead to confusion if it is moved out of the main class list. I'll defer to the site admins as it's their call at the end of the day how the main page is structured.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14022594#post-4920461</guid>
				<title>Should Blood Hunter be moved to the Homebrew section?</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14022594/should-blood-hunter-be-moved-to-the-homebrew-section#post-4920461</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2021 14:45:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Valkyria Grey</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6675660</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Given that there's been a lot of changes happening on the site, such as the addition of Mystic and moving Rune Scribe to the UA section (and great job to all of you who are working on adding and organizing content), it begs the question if Blood Hunter should be moved to the Homebrew section? I not saying it definitely should, but I wanted to see if anyone had any thoughts about it.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>