<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Front page edit request: Obsolete UA Mystic / Rune Scribe</title>
		<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14007714/front-page-edit-request:obsolete-ua-mystic-rune-scribe</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Front page edit request: Obsolete UA Mystic / Rune Scribe&quot; - edit the front page to make the mystic visible and move the rune scribe</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 01:00:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14007714#post-4916528</guid>
				<title>Re: Front page edit request: Obsolete UA Mystic / Rune Scribe</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14007714/front-page-edit-request:obsolete-ua-mystic-rune-scribe#post-4916528</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 12:41:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Thank you Fred !</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14007714#post-4914102</guid>
				<title>Re: Front page edit request: Obsolete UA Mystic / Rune Scribe</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14007714/front-page-edit-request:obsolete-ua-mystic-rune-scribe#post-4914102</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 18:49:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fredbob711</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6144441</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Mystic has been added to the main page under Archived Unearthed Arcana, and Rune Scribe has been moved into the same section.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14007714#post-4906201</guid>
				<title>Re: Front page edit request: Obsolete UA Mystic / Rune Scribe</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14007714/front-page-edit-request:obsolete-ua-mystic-rune-scribe#post-4906201</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 22:36:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>A spreadsheet?</p> <p>Yeah now that sounds like a good start</p> <p>ill send you a message then, ill probably work on the backgrounds</p> <p>thanks (:</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14007714#post-4903789</guid>
				<title>Re: Front page edit request: Obsolete UA Mystic / Rune Scribe</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14007714/front-page-edit-request:obsolete-ua-mystic-rune-scribe#post-4903789</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 15:47:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>cottoneyenoh</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>5928724</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>congrats on finishing the mystic! the only things I can think of that need work on here are adding backgrounds and working on the wondrous items page.</p> <p>we still need to add backgrounds from horde of the dragon queen, out of the abyss, ghosts of saltmarch, curse of strahd's optional backgrounds, state of hillsfar, the mulmaster bonds and backgrounds, acquisitions inc., and mythic odysseys of theros. i've had some experience with adding backgrounds (i added the ravnica guilds), and they're a bit of a pain, but if you want something to do, adding the 32 backgrounds could be a nice diversion. if you need a list of the specific backgrounds, message me (i've got a spreadsheet with everything i know that we need to add to the wiki lol)</p> <p>as for wondrous items, i've been chipping away at it for a while, but i've been a bit overwhelmed by work in the real world, so i haven't touched it in a while. it's just adding pages for each item listed in the chart (which, unfortunately, is about 250 items left across the different sources). it's a big undertaking, but feel free to tackle some of it if you want.</p> <p>obviously, don't overwork yourself, but if you want stuff to take on, those could be places to start</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14007714#post-4903047</guid>
				<title>Front page edit request: Obsolete UA Mystic / Rune Scribe</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14007714/front-page-edit-request:obsolete-ua-mystic-rune-scribe#post-4903047</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 02:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>So! The mystic finally is completed, subpages and all! Every last discipline. Id like to say thanks to everyone who helped out (Especially thanks for un-fucking the formatting for the disciplines pages).</p> <p>Yeah its been a fun on and off these last few weeks just adding discipline pages</p> <p>So yeah, in a previous discussion thread it was said we would be placing the Mystic page to the obsolete UA section, aswell as moving the rune scribe from the main classes section to the obsolete UA section aswell. Now that the mystic is complete, it is now appropriate to move it to the front page for viewing. These changes are already available on the home:test</p> <p>once again, thanks everyone and uh&#8230; yeah now i dont really have anything to do with my free time.. i was kinda just sitting there adding pages this whole while&#8230; anything else the wiki needs at the moment? god WoTC please release new UA</p> <p>&lt;3</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>