<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Epic boons (and abberent dragonmark feats)</title>
		<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14120019/epic-boons-and-abberent-dragonmark-feats</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Epic boons (and abberent dragonmark feats)&quot; - A page for epic boons, aswell as the abberant dragon mark feats</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:59:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14120019#post-5016954</guid>
				<title>Re: Epic boons (and abberent dragonmark feats)</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14120019/epic-boons-and-abberent-dragonmark-feats#post-5016954</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 12:31:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ah thats fair reasoning. I personally feel that under the 'different enough to warrant separate pages rule this feat could apply, due to their main feature being completely different (Despite holding the same name), that of the book version allowing you to expend hit dice to deal either additonal damage or gain temp HP randomly, while the UA version allowed you to upcast a spell beyond its level in exchange for dealing damage to yourself and exhausting a hit die. So overall its a bit of an outlier i guess in comparison to feats that go from UA to the books unchanged</p> <p>Yeah, a misc section could make sense, but I feel we'd need a good bunch of differernt things to make it worth the effort yet.</p> <p>If there are suggestions for pages that would be nice to have to go into the misc page, I could potentially find the time to add them to the site</p> <p>Edit: Oh! The sidekick subclasses could go quite nicely in there actually! I made them all just a bit back, so if we did make a misc section, they'd slot right in there</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14120019#post-5016458</guid>
				<title>Re: Epic boons (and abberent dragonmark feats)</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14120019/epic-boons-and-abberent-dragonmark-feats#post-5016458</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 22:54:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fredbob711</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6144441</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Added the Abberant Dragonmark feat to the main page. I think we generally remove/rename UA feats when they get officially published, I know we're not doing that for subclasses, but subclasses are more involved and usually have more changes to them between UA and officially published material.</p> <p>For Epic Boons, I'm not sure where those would go on the main page. It would almost need to be a Miscellaneous section for anything that doesn't fit into a category&#8230; Have to think about that.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14120019#post-5016035</guid>
				<title>Re: Epic boons (and abberent dragonmark feats)</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14120019/epic-boons-and-abberent-dragonmark-feats#post-5016035</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 12:26:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I like the formatting, very nice</p> <p>Hm, as for its place on the frontpage, it doesnt really have a spot that it would slot into, and would really need a whole section on its one for it. And for something that takes a whole section on its own, it really isnt that important to justify it. So yeah, unless we add a bunch of other similiar such pages (Such as the van richten dark gifts), but I dont think it warrents its not category. Not without a bunch of similiar things to put with it. So for now, its probably best just existing as something that is linked to on the feats page.<br /> However, I am intrigued by the idea now that i think of it to have a section (probably below the feats section) for epic boons and supernatural charms (Things such as dark gift and etc), the supernatural gifts from Theros, hollow ones from wildemount and other such features and traits that you pick up while adventuring, as opposed to character creation.</p> <p>(Oh! also, for the epic boons page, I found that the DMG lists a variant option that can be taken place instead of an epic boon, that of an asi (that can go to a max of 30) or an additional feat, do you think this should be listed, and if so, where would it look best in the page to be listed. Page 230 of the dmg btw)</p> <p>Sorta like items, in a sense, but rather than objects you pick up its things that have modified your character and given them little bonus traits.</p> <p>I dunno, what are your thoughts?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14120019#post-5008247</guid>
				<title>Re: Epic boons (and abberent dragonmark feats)</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14120019/epic-boons-and-abberent-dragonmark-feats#post-5008247</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 04:22:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>cottoneyenoh</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>5928724</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>forgot to mention when i did it, i made some edits to format it like our eldritch invocations page, add a table of contents, etc. i like having it available, im just not sure where it fits on the front page. maybe its enough to be linked to in the erlw abberant dragonmark page and have it be something to be searched if people need it?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14120019#post-5005383</guid>
				<title>Epic boons (and abberent dragonmark feats)</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14120019/epic-boons-and-abberent-dragonmark-feats#post-5005383</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 23:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I created an epic boons page on the wikidot due to epic boons being referenced by the abberant dragonmark feat, which can be found at <a href="http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/epic-boons">http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/epic-boons</a> in case someone else has a need for it, or sees that it should be placed on the homepage for some reason.</p> <p>And here are the abberant dragon mark feats,</p> <p>UA version: <a href="http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/feat:abberant-dragonmark-ua">http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/feat:abberant-dragonmark-ua</a><br /> Ebberon Rising from the Last War version: <a href="http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/feat:abberant-dragonmark">http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/feat:abberant-dragonmark</a></p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>