<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wikidot="http://www.wikidot.com/rss-namespace">

	<channel>
		<title>Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
		<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul</link>
		<description>Posts in the discussion thread &quot;Update on backgrounds + favored soul&quot;</description>
				<copyright></copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 21:58:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
		
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726#post-4927937</guid>
				<title>Re: Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul#post-4927937</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 01:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>While not in my list of backgrounds that I was given to be able to work on them, Ive found that EGW (Explorers guide to wildemount) also apparently has backgrounds aswell.</p> <p>Should the Wildemount backgrounds recieve pages? I believe so, since they are an official setting for 5e now that wotc has released a setting book for it.</p> <p>Edit: Disregard. The majority of wildemount backgrounds are renamed/alterations to base game backgrounds. The unique backgrounds already have pages</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726#post-4922324</guid>
				<title>Re: Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul#post-4922324</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 12:16:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hm, yeah that could make sense. For example, the 'deep delver' and 'under dark experience' could link to the same 'Background:Out-Of-the-Abyss' page, but that may end up being confusing <sub>and ive already made pages for them so&#8230;</sub> and it should be fine for them to have their own pages. I mean, afterall, they are kinda weird, since they are essentially variant backgrounds which are designed to go with any background&#8230; So I think leaving them with their own pages is good</p> <p>As for the backgrounds, ive progressed through about half of them, and I should be capable at progressing at a slightly faster pace from here on out due to having an abundance of free time upon me.</p> <p>Ill make a 'All the backgrounds are finished post' once they are all completed, rather than flooding the discussions with individual 'page completed' posts. Also, that way the frontpage can be updated all at once, and that should be pretty cool to see a sudden large expansion.</p> <p>I look forward to being able to share them all with you soon :)</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726#post-4921994</guid>
				<title>Re: Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul#post-4921994</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 01:12:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>Fredbob711</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6144441</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I'm going to work on the Backgrounds section of the main page later this week. I'll get it split up by setting and see if anything else makes sense.</p> <p>For the variants that aren't full backgrounds, we do have the option of directing a link from the main page to the specific variant section of the background page. If you look at the link for the 'Spy' background for the main page, it actually just links to the 'Criminal' background and automatically scrolls the page to the Spy variant section.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726#post-4919754</guid>
				<title>Re: Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul#post-4919754</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 22:58:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Ah yeah, thatd make sense</p> <p>have them listed as variant features on their page, and split them into seperate categories</p> <p>thanks</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726#post-4919496</guid>
				<title>Re: Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul#post-4919496</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 15:05:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>cottoneyenoh</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>5928724</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I think that like the Revenant background, having pages for those backgrounds that expresses that they're replacements for background features would probably work. The alternative is just not adding them I guess since it's not feasible or worthwhile to add the option to every other background. Maybe if we do sort the backgrounds into something like &quot;generic&quot;, &quot;setting-specific&quot;, and whatever else, those can be put in a category of &quot;unique&quot;?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726#post-4919047</guid>
				<title>Re: Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul#post-4919047</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 05:16:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>alright, yeah that makes sense. Sure,</p> <p>Ill be continuing with the page creation for the backgrounds when ive got time to do so again,</p> <p>note: Among the list of backgrounds that needed pages for the website, ive noticed some of them were not actual backgrounds but optional replacement features for your background, such as OotA's 'Deep Delver' or 'Underdark Experience'.</p> <p>what should be done with those ones? theres not alot, but they do exist</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726#post-4918704</guid>
				<title>Re: Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul#post-4918704</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 19:03:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>cottoneyenoh</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>5928724</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>I think that the Revenant works better as its own page under our UA section than as being listed as a subrace for the few examples listed in the original UA it came from. The article mentions how there's no subraces for half-elves and half-orcs (which we know is wrong) and doesn't mention the other races that it could theoretically apply to (elves, dwarves, and the variety of races that were released after the article was published), so keeping it as its own standalone page works better imo.</p> <p>Our Backgrounds section could certainly use some adjustment, separating the generic backgrounds (fisher, hermit, etc) from the setting specific backgrounds (the Ravnica guilds and most of the backgrounds that still need to be added). I think that formatting it to match our Races section might work, but that's a decision for Fredbob or the admin to make.</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726#post-4918306</guid>
				<title>Re: Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul#post-4918306</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 10:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Currently, Revenent is its own page, however, since it is technically just a set of subcraces, wouldnt it be better to instead update the dragonborn / human pages to have them as listed subraces, rather than its own page?</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726#post-4916165</guid>
				<title>Re: Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul#post-4916165</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 23:21:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>also, currently I believe the background section could use a touch up. The planeshift backgrounds are seperated, but ravnica, ebberon and forgotten realms backgrounds are currently mixed together. So the backgrounds setting should be touched up further to seperate all the backgrounds by their settings</p> <p>~~~</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726#post-4916145</guid>
				<title>Re: Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul#post-4916145</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 22:40:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>oh and yeah, I feel like we should have a page for the 'spell less' ranger variant aswell, just like we have the revised</p> <p>should be mostly simple to make, copy and paste the default ranger features, and swap in the spell less ranger features</p> <p>of course, the issue to start with is page link name</p> <p>my first thought is just '<a href="http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/ranger-no-spells-ua">http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/ranger-no-spells-ua</a>', but that doesnt seem like a very good link. Sucks the class variant is just called 'Ranger with no spells'</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726#post-4915765</guid>
				<title>Re: Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul#post-4915765</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 13:09:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p><a href="http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/revenant">http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/revenant</a></p> <p>oh yeah and heres the revenant</p> <p>probably should go into the ua races</p> <p>imma be homest i dont really like the race because its formatted weird, and kinda, no, completely OP</p> <p>but whatever, wotc made it, and as such it needs to be archived</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
					<item>
				<guid>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726#post-4915755</guid>
				<title>Update on backgrounds + favored soul</title>
				<link>http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/forum/t-14017726/update-on-backgrounds-favored-soul#post-4915755</link>
				<description></description>
				<pubDate>Wed, 03 Mar 2021 12:56:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<wikidot:authorName>NCat</wikidot:authorName>				<wikidot:authorUserId>6662241</wikidot:authorUserId>				<content:encoded>
					<![CDATA[
						 <p>Hey alright so ive begun work on the pile of backgrounds we are yet to add in, but im no where near finishing it (Because god damn it school). So, be aware I am working on it still, and it will be done in time, and I will make a post listing off all the backgrounds that need to be added.</p> <p>but on the plus side, I decided to add in the old favored soul UA, <a href="http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/sorcerer:favored-soul-ua">http://dnd5e.wikidot.com/sorcerer:favored-soul-ua</a>, Bam. Unearthed arcana 3? Yeah, what a low number huh</p> <p>well ive already added it do the sorcerer page, it just needs to be added to the obsolete UA on the frontpage too</p> <p>&lt;3 yeah thanks !</p> 
				 	]]>
				</content:encoded>							</item>
				</channel>
</rss>